<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <GD.StationTitle>Mech-Communication Station: Operation Page</GD.StationTitle>
  <GD.StationDescription>This seemingly simple device is capable of capturing electromagnetic waves generated by communication among mechanoids, and tracing back the path to locate the position of mechanoid servers. Experienced researchers can use this to infiltrate servers, intercept a portion of intelligence, and then use it for sale or other purposes. Mechanoid intelligence is classified into five levels of secrecy, and typically, we can only intercept the lowest two levels, as intelligence from the third level onward requires physical keys to unlock.\n\nCurrently holding Level One intelligence: {0}\nCurrently holding Level Two intelligence: {1}</GD.StationDescription>
  <GD.CommunicateWithEmpire>Contacting the Empire…</GD.CommunicateWithEmpire>
  <GD.EmpireNotFound>(No Empire Faction)</GD.EmpireNotFound>
  <GD.CommunicateWithBlackMech>Contacting the Black Mechanoid Hive…</GD.CommunicateWithBlackMech>
  <GD.WaitForDiscover>(No Signal)</GD.WaitForDiscover>
  <GD.FirewallStable>Current status of mechanoid server: Stable\nSafe to infiltrate and intercept intelligence.</GD.FirewallStable>
  <GD.FirewallUnstable>Current status of mechanoid server: Unstable\nChance to intercept more intelligence, but also risks exposure.</GD.FirewallUnstable>
  <GD.FirewallAlert>Current status of mechanoid server: Alert\nCease intelligence interception immediately!</GD.FirewallAlert>
  <GD.EmpireTaxTip>Due to the Empire’s long-standing involvement and establishment of comprehensive laws and regulations regarding mechanical intelligence, you are required to pay a 10% tax on each piece of data you obtain.\nUnless you plan to show your hand.</GD.EmpireTaxTip>
  <GD.EmpireTaxHostile>Due to hostility with the Empire, you are exempt from paying taxes.</GD.EmpireTaxHostile>
  <GD.FirewallToUnstable>The firewall for the mechanoid server has been updated. Current status: Unstable</GD.FirewallToUnstable>
  <GD.FirewallToStable>The firewall for the mechanoid server has been updated. Current status: Stable</GD.FirewallToStable>
  <GD.FirewallToAlert>The firewall for the mechanoid server has been updated. Current status: Alert</GD.FirewallToAlert>
  <GD.RevengeRaid>An unsafe operation drew the attention of the mechanoids. Their revenge is coming!</GD.RevengeRaid>
  <GD.ExtraInt>Extra Intelligence!</GD.ExtraInt>
  <GD.ToggleLabel>primary processing:{0}</GD.ToggleLabel>
  <GD.ToggleDesc>Restore information processing to a low-level form to intercept primary intelligence.</GD.ToggleDesc>
  <!-- empire -->
  <GD.EmpireTradeTitle>Mech-Communication Station: Trade with the Empire</GD.EmpireTradeTitle>
  <GD.EmpireTradeDescription>You can exchange mechanoid intelligence with the Empire for silver, honor, or simply to improve relations.</GD.EmpireTradeDescription>
  <GD.EmpireSellInt1>Selling primary intelligence: You currently hold {0} units</GD.EmpireSellInt1>
  <GD.SellIntButton_1Silver>Exchange for Silver (1000 intelligence - 200 silver)</GD.SellIntButton_1Silver>
  <GD.SellIntButton_1Royal>Exchange for Honor (1000 intelligence - 2 honor)</GD.SellIntButton_1Royal>
  <GD.SellIntButton_1Relation>Improve Relations (1000 intelligence - 8 relation)</GD.SellIntButton_1Relation>
  <GD.EmpireSellInt2>Selling advanced intelligence: You currently hold {0} units</GD.EmpireSellInt2>
  <GD.SellIntButton_2Silver>Exchange for Silver (1000 intelligence - 500 silver)</GD.SellIntButton_2Silver>
  <GD.SellIntButton_2Royal>Exchange for Honor (1000 intelligence - 5 honor)</GD.SellIntButton_2Royal>
  <GD.SellIntButton_2Relation>Improve Relations (1000 intelligence - 15 relation)</GD.SellIntButton_2Relation>
  <GD.EmpireSellHostile>Due to hostility with the Empire, most trading options are currently unavailable.\nThe high stellarch {0} indicates he needs to see your sincerity. Currently, you can only improve relations using intelligence until the rift between the two factions is largely eliminated.</GD.EmpireSellHostile>
  <GD.IntNotEnough>Your intelligence is insufficient.</GD.IntNotEnough>
  <GD.Back>Back</GD.Back>
  <!-- BlackMechanoid -->
  <GD.ContainCorpse>The coffin does contain a corpse, but there is no dark or rotten smell.</GD.ContainCorpse>
  <GD.BlackMechAlreadyDiscovered>Black Mechanoid Hive already discovered</GD.BlackMechAlreadyDiscovered>
  <GD.LevelNotEnoughToAnalyse>Intellectual level less than 10</GD.LevelNotEnoughToAnalyse>
  <GD.DamageBlack>Due to aggressive behavior, your relationship with the Black Mechanoid Hive has decreased by {0} points.</GD.DamageBlack>
  <GD.BlackHostileTitle>Hostile: Black Mechanoid Hive</GD.BlackHostileTitle>
  <GD.BlackHostileDesc>Your overzealous actions have disappointed the Black Mechanoid Hive. If encountered again, they will consider you as an enemy.</GD.BlackHostileDesc>
  <GD.QuestNotFinish>Only a noisy rustling sound is heard from the other end, perhaps you need to complete your current task first.</GD.QuestNotFinish>
  <GD.NeedPayTitle>Current task requires payment of intelligence</GD.NeedPayTitle>
  <GD.NeedPayDesc>The next task from the Black Mechanoid Hive requires you to pay intelligence to be issued. This could be a test of your willingness to cooperate, or to prepare for future actions.\n\nRequires {0}: {1}\nYou currently have: {2}</GD.NeedPayDesc>
  <GD.NeedPayButton>Pay</GD.NeedPayButton>
  <GD.PaymentSuccess>You have handed over the intelligence to the Mechanoid Hive, contact them again for the next task.</GD.PaymentSuccess>
  <GD.PrimaryInt>Primary Intel</GD.PrimaryInt>
  <GD.PrimaryAdv>Advanced Intel</GD.PrimaryAdv>
  <GD.BlackMechSellInt>Sell Advanced Intel: You currently have {0} pieces</GD.BlackMechSellInt>
  <GD.BlackMechScriptTree>Progress</GD.BlackMechScriptTree>
  <GD.BlackMechScriptTreeEnd>(Finished)</GD.BlackMechScriptTreeEnd>
  <GD.BlackMechTradeTitle>Mechanical Communicator: Black Mechanoid Hive</GD.BlackMechTradeTitle>
  <GD.BlackMechTradeDescription>Unlike regular mechanoids, members of the Black Mechanoid Hive lean more towards neutrality towards humans - which means that if you bring them something valuable, they may give something in return. You can exchange intelligence with them for resources, or do something for them.</GD.BlackMechTradeDescription>
  <GD.BlackMechTradeUnable>Your colony does not yet have enough understanding of this faction.\nProgress to unlock functionality on this page.</GD.BlackMechTradeUnable>
  <Reward_BlackMech_Label>Black Mechanoid Task</Reward_BlackMech_Label>
  <Reward_BlackMech>This is a task given by the Black Mechanoid Hive, complete it to progress.</Reward_BlackMech>
  <Reward_Intelligence_Label>Intelligence exchange</Reward_Intelligence_Label>
  <Reward_Intelligence>The Black Mechanoid Hive will share 2,500 secondary intelligence points with you as an additional fee.</Reward_Intelligence>
  <GD.ApocritonIsDead>Black Apocriton is dead</GD.ApocritonIsDead>
  <GD.BlackMechNotFound>No black mechanoid hive found</GD.BlackMechNotFound>
  <GD.BlackMechNotEnemy>Black mechanoid hive is not your enemy</GD.BlackMechNotEnemy>
  <!-- Subcore -->
  <GD.SubcoreRaidTitle>Mechanoids Raid</GD.SubcoreRaidTitle>
  <GD.SubcoreRaidDesc>The subcore accidentally emitted a burst of chaotic electromagnetic waves during research, immediately attracting the attention of a nearby detachment of mechanoids. Prepare for battle.</GD.SubcoreRaidDesc>
  <GD.SubcoreBadEvent1Title>Firelight</GD.SubcoreBadEvent1Title>
  <GD.SubcoreBadEvent1Desc>The subcore suddenly burst into flames during research.</GD.SubcoreBadEvent1Desc>
  <GD.SubcoreBadEvent2Title>Thick Smoke</GD.SubcoreBadEvent2Title>
  <GD.SubcoreBadEvent2Desc>The subcore suddenly emitted a burst of thick smoke during research.</GD.SubcoreBadEvent2Desc>
  <GD.SubcoreProgress>Progress: {0}/{1}</GD.SubcoreProgress>
  <GD.SubcoreCooldown>Can research again in {0} hours.</GD.SubcoreCooldown>
  <GD.SendSubcore>Manually send back</GD.SendSubcore>
  <GD.SendSubcoreDesc>Click this button if the subcore is not automatically returned.</GD.SendSubcoreDesc>
  <!-- Server -->
  <GD.ServerStolen>Interacted with this server before</GD.ServerStolen>
  <GD.KeyNeeded>Key required</GD.KeyNeeded>
  <GD.ServerStealComplete>Part of the intelligence has been stolen: {0}/{1}</GD.ServerStealComplete>
  <GD.KeyGained>Permission obtained, you can now interact with the server in the mechanoid fortress.</GD.KeyGained>
  <GD.HasKey>Permission obtained</GD.HasKey>
  <!-- Militor -->
  <MilitorAlert>Guard target</MilitorAlert>
  <MilitorAlertDesc>Detected mechanoid forces approaching the area. Your job is to guard the militor. If his actions are likely to put him in danger, you need to use psycast or EMP means to stop him immediately. </MilitorAlertDesc>
  <GD.MilitorMissionStart>Mechanoid forces are detected approaching. The first wave of attacks will appear in 60 seconds. Deploy defenses as soon as possible. </GD.MilitorMissionStart>
  <GD.RaidLight>Advance Assault</GD.RaidLight>
  <GD.RaidLightDesc>A fast-response mechanoid's force has arrived nearby. Prepare for defense.</GD.RaidLightDesc>
  <GD.RaidHeavy>Main Assault</GD.RaidHeavy>
  <GD.RaidHeavyDesc>A powerful mechanoid's main force has arrived nearby. Prepare for defense.</GD.RaidHeavyDesc>
  <GD.RaidUltraHeavy>Final Assault</GD.RaidUltraHeavy>
  <GD.RaidUltraHeavyDesc>The final assault by the mechanoid hive is imminent. Withstand this powerful pressure!</GD.RaidUltraHeavyDesc>
  <GD.HelpArrive>Reinforcements have arrived nearby and will immediately assist in the battle.</GD.HelpArrive>
  <GD.MilitorExiting>The militor is preparing to leave the map, pay attention to protect him.</GD.MilitorExiting>
  <!-- Eliminate -->
  <GD.FoundMilitor>Black Militor has been found, and soon he will be sent back to headquarters, ready to find the traitor and fight.</GD.FoundMilitor>
  <GD.FoundMilitorCorpse>We are late. Prepare to search for traitors and fight.</GD.FoundMilitorCorpse>
  <GD.ReadyToBattle>Prepare to search for traitors and fight.</GD.ReadyToBattle>
  <GD.BattleStart>Target appeared</GD.BattleStart>
  <GD.BattleStartDesc>The enemy has appeared. It seems they have been lying in ambush here for a long time. Eliminate them!</GD.BattleStartDesc>
  <GD.TesseronSay>Since you already know, I have nothing more to say!</GD.TesseronSay>
  <GD.DollReward>Achievement reward: Complete the “Eliminate Traitors” task and keep the black militor alive.</GD.DollReward>
  <!-- Exostrider -->
  <GD.MortarHacked>The mortar is under control</GD.MortarHacked>
  <GD.ExostriderIntro>Invincibility status.</GD.ExostriderIntro>
  <GD.Exostrider2Intro>Only giant mortars can damage this unit.</GD.Exostrider2Intro>
  <GD.ExostriderStartFight>The exostrider is about to destroy a giant mortar that has changed hands!</GD.ExostriderStartFight>
  <GD.ExoBeamAttack>Exostrider called for orbital beam support. Watch out!</GD.ExoBeamAttack>
  <GD.ExoBombardmentAttack>Exostrider calls in orbital bombing support. Watch out!</GD.ExoBombardmentAttack>
  <GD.ExoMechanoids>Mechanoids airdrop reinforcements</GD.ExoMechanoids>
  <GD.ExoMechanoidsDesc>A large number of mechs are coming out of hibernation and dropping from orbit to support the battle, watch out for incoming enemies in all directions.</GD.ExoMechanoidsDesc>
  <GD.ExoSuperBeamAttack>Exostrider calls a wave of orbital beam saturation bombardment. Be careful to avoid!</GD.ExoSuperBeamAttack>
  <ExostriderAlert>Mechanoid ships assembly</ExostriderAlert>
  <ExostriderAlertDesc>The mechanoid ships' attention is gradually returning to the exostrider. End the fight as soon as possible, or you will be subjected to increasing fire suppression.</ExostriderAlertDesc>
  <GD.MortarLost>We have lost a giant mortar.</GD.MortarLost>
  <GD.MortarAllLost>All the giant mortars are destroyed, and we have no way to damage the exostrider. Fall back now!</GD.MortarAllLost>
  
  <GD.ChipReward>Achievement Bonus: Complete the entire Black Quest Line.</GD.ChipReward>
  <GD.ScriptEnd>Quest line complete</GD.ScriptEnd>
  <GD.ScriptEndDesc>You have completed the Black Quest Line. \n\nThe Black Mechanoid Hive is out of contact with you, but you can still trade with them with intelligence.\n\nIf you own a black mechanitor uniform, you should notice that it has reached level five.</GD.ScriptEndDesc>
  
  <GD.CantGenerateQuest>Quest acceptance failed. It might be due to reasons such as missing colony maps. Please check.</GD.CantGenerateQuest>
</LanguageData>